chinesemov.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy - chinesemov.com

Privacy Policy

Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the chinesemov.com website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers chinesemov.com's treatment of personal information that chinesemov.com gathers when you are on the chinesemov.com website. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that chinesemov.com does not own or control, or to individuals that chinesemov.com does not employ or manage.

General  
chinesemov.com does not collect personally identifiable information except when you expressly volunteer the information. chinesemov.com collects some information that is relevant to the purpose of our website when you visit chinesemov.com pages. chinesemov.com may combine information that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. chinesemov.com automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.   
chinesemov.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see,  improve our services, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

Cookies  
-Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Our cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are.   
-The "Help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies.   
-Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on our website. 

chinesemov.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com

Changes to this Policy  
This information will be revised or updated if practices change.

Copyright © 2011 [chinesemov.com](http://chinesemov.com/index.html)
